Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series are fictional and
created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
My boss wants to collaborate with you.
Mr. Thee, I don’t think
I can make it to dinner anymore.
Based on the information we found,
she dated Mr. Peach back in university.
Tomorrow’s a day off. Are you free?
There’s somewhere I’d like to take you.
This is my real life.
What’s been stressing you out all day?
Are you afraid I’d mind
that you grew up there?
I don’t want to think that way,
but I can’t help it.
Knowing this makes me love you even more.
How about we try dating?
I swear I’ll love, take care of,
and protect you and your sister for life.
4-inch stilettos.
You haven’t learned, huh?
I can walk on my own now.
No need for anyone to hold me up.
Are you doing well?
Yeah, I’m okay.
This is Mr. Touch.
He’s my boss.
This is Peach.
Nice to finally meet you, Mr. Peachayarat.
Yes.
I’m really sorry for asking Mim
to reach out to you privately.
We really want to work with you,
but we couldn’t reach you at all.
No worries. I’m currently in
a long-term project with another company,
so I haven’t been taking on other jobs.
ARSENI?
Yes. You know it?
Only a few people don’t know it.
Anyway,
what would a mafia family
need a photographer for?
Oh, I’m working for
Mr. Theerakit’s perfume business.
So they use perfume for money laundering?
By the way, what’s the scope
of the project you want to hire me for?
Shohei is launching
an artist management company.
We currently have a few models signed.
We want you to take their profile photos
and shoot content to promote our company.
When’s the launch?
Hmm.
As soon as possible would be great,
but we’ll work around your schedule.
Oh, if you’re really in a rush
and it’s just a profile shoot,
I can actually recommend
some other good photographers.
No way, Peach.
You promised me.
I just don’t want to keep you waiting.
I can wait.
I only want you, Mr. Peach.
Have you been waiting long?
Now I know who’s going to be
the first to have their eyeballs removed.
Calm down.
How can I?
Every time he looks at you,
it’s like he wants to eat you up.
I’m a human. How could he eat me?
But I already ate you up.
You can’t say that!
Where should we go?
Your place?
I’m going home.
You’re going back to work.
Can’t I go with you?
No.
I’m not feeling well.
I feel feverish and shivery.
I guess I’ll have to take sick leave.
If you’re sick, go to the hospital,
not my house.
Fine.
But if it turns out I’m really sick,
you have to let me sleep over
at your house
and take care of me
without leaving my side.
Mok, take me to the hospital.
An ARSENI hospital...
where doctors can give medical
certificates the way you want them?
Or which hospital, Boss?
Mok!
You’re so sneaky, Mr. Thee.
What did I do wrong?
I just don’t want to be away
from my boyfriend.
You’ve hit me twice already, Lookpeach.
Let’s go, Mr. Mok.
Please take me home
and take Mr. Thee to the office.
Got it.
Give me his name card.
You’re off work now, Mok.
I’m sorry.
What’s wrong?
Sorry?
Are you saying you drink all the time?
I just couldn’t sleep,
so I came down to chill for a bit.
Congratulations on Peach.
This is not the end, and you know it.
But it’s a really good beginning,
isn’t it?
I know now why love is dangerous for us.
Do you understand what Master
has been trying to tell us now?
I was never afraid of dying
until I fell in love with Peach.
ARSENI’s bodyguards are taught
to see death as something close.
It’s probably right
that I should stay away from love.
But you’re not just a bodyguard.
You’re my friend, Mok.
You’re happy that I found Peach.
I want to be happy for you, too.
Still,
in the end,
I have to take a bullet for my friend.
But as long as ARSENI
is under my supervision,
no one will die.
-Peach!
-Oh!
You’re startled, huh?
Ran!
What are you doing here?
They said there are
a few more details to discuss.
What about you? What are you doing here?
Hi, Mr. Peach.
Mr. Touch.
Mim.
Glad to see you, Peach.
What brings you two here?
This is Tawan.
He’s a model under Shohei
and another presenter for
the Spring Collection.
We’ll be working together
sooner than I thought.
The special scent for the Fall Collection,
our special project,
was very well received,
so ARSENI wants to invite you
to work with us fully
for the Spring Collection, Mr. Tawan.
It’s a great pleasure
that Shohei has accepted our offer.
The pleasure is all mine.
I've personally been wanting to come back.
Partnering with a famous model like you
on such a big project like this,
Tawan might need your help
with a lot of things, Mr. Aran.
No problem.
There shouldn’t be any issues
since they’ve worked together before.
Yes, we get along well.
It’s lunch break,
and all the places are packed.
Are you hungry?
Not yet.
You’re lying. I know you eat on time.
What would you like to eat?
Name the place.
Why?
Are you going to use your power again?
ARSENI has shares
in some of the restaurants.
It’s not unusual for them
to keep a special table for the owner.
No.
I don’t want to see people
getting chased out of a restaurant.
I never chase anyone out empty-handed.
The compensation I give them
for their wasted time
might even be enough
for them to enjoy 10 free—
(Get a grip!)
—meals.
But I probably won’t do that.
I won’t do it anymore.
You suddenly got it together, huh?
I don’t want to be scolded by you.
Besides scolding you,
I don’t want you using your money
to interfere in other people’s lives.
I get it now.
From now on, I’ll focus on saving money
just for you to use.
Eat this to tide you over for now.
Once the restaurants clear out,
we can have a proper meal.
It’s a little hot here,
but it’s the most peaceful spot.
If I’d known you’d be this cute
as my boyfriend,
I’d have sealed you as mine
in our past life.
You like it?
Yeah.
I love eating this
when I’m busy with work.
One hand working, the other eating.
It’s easy.
What do you think?
It’s good.
Actually, you can just tell me
what you’d like to eat next time.
I can have Mok prepare it in my office,
so we don’t have to
fight over it with others like this.
It’s just lining up for restaurants,
not fighting over them.
Besides, I don’t want to
keep going in and out of your room.
Don’t forget that others
still don’t know about us.
I have a meeting with the executive board
the day after tomorrow.
How about I announce our relationship
right in the middle of the meeting?
But if that’s too late,
I can issue a statement and
circulate it to all departments first.
WHERE DID YOU GO? I WAS GONNA…
I don’t mind if other people
know about us.
I only care about one person.
WHERE DID YOU GO?
I WAS GONNA INVITE YOU TO LUNCH.
Yes, already.
I saw you were busy, so I slipped out.
Sorry.
Let’s eat together next time.
Okay.
Do your best at work.
You think Panachakorn won’t like me?
It’s not that she won’t like you.
I just need to find the right time
and opportunity to tell her.
If she finds out from someone else,
she’ll probably make a fuss.
Her big brother is just dating.
Is it really that big of a deal?
It normally wouldn’t be,
but it is because it’s you.
Think about it.
Her brother and her boss are dating.
And in Plub’s eyes,
you’re not exactly a kind boss.
I’ve taken care of Rome a bit before.
I’ll try to dig up whatever little bit of
‘older brother’ I have and use it.
Thank you.
Whatever you’re carrying,
put it down and let me help you carry it.
About that model, too.
You mean Tawan?
The marketing team
just proposed his name this morning.
I haven’t approved it yet.
I wanted to ask you first.
Actually, I don’t have
any issues with Tawan.
We can just work and get it over with.
Aran also said he doesn’t want to
mix work with personal matters.
I’d be more worried about Tawan.
Who knows what trouble he’ll cause again?
I can replace him if you want.
Let’s go with what the team wants.
I don’t want to involve personal matters.
Besides, if Aran finds out
his personal issues
are affecting the team,
he won’t be happy.
You’re only worrying about
other people again.
Well…
That’s because I already have you
looking out for me.
Wait, Peach.
I have one more thing to tell you.
Tatsuya is not an ordinary man
like you think he is.
The Shohei family is no different from
my father’s Lee family.
Mr. Touch is a mafia boss too?
I’ve had people
keep an eye on you for now,
but you can live normally.
My men won’t make you feel uncomfortable.
So this is the real life
I have to face, huh?
Are you afraid?
I believe you won’t let anything
happen to me.
Thanks for helping me, dude.
You know I’m not helping you for free.
I just want Aran back.
You can take whatever you want.
I can’t wait to see
what ARSENI is really capable of.
Hey!
Mr. Thee.
Did I startle you?
Don’t do that again.
Sorry.
It’s okay.
You have work at the studio today, right?
We’re just doing fittings today,
but it’s a big one
before we shoot on location.
Are you tired?
If you are, you can rest in my office.
Tired? I just got here.
I haven’t even taken my camera out
to set anything up yet.
I have a meeting this morning,
but I’ll come down to see you
as soon as it’s over.
Do your best at work.
(Do your best at work.)
I love you.
Do you wuv me?
Mr. Thee.
Do you wuv me, Lookpeach?
I love you too.
Peach and Boss…
Boss and Peach…
Oh my! I’m going to faint.
Come on. Let me help.
-It’s okay.
-Let me help.
Thank you.
What a coincidence
to be working together again.
So it’s really like I thought.
Well, I didn’t know
how else to approach you.
I called, but you didn’t pick up.
I texted, but you didn’t reply.
Don’t you think that’s because...
I don’t want anything
to do with you anymore?
But I’m still in love with you.
Very much.
Ran, can I have another chance?
This can be the last time.
I’m sorry,
but I’m not in love
with you anymore, Tawan.
You’ve settled in now?
I feel much more comfortable
being your assistant.
Don’t hold back, Peach.
I’d even carry a house if you ask.
Just let me know when you need anything.
Uh…
It’s such an honor that you came down
to oversee the work yourself, Boss.
If I hadn’t, I wouldn’t have realized
how much attention the photographer gets.
You can take the whole bag, Mr. Thee
Please have a seat here, Boss.
Alright.
Come on, everyone.
Okay.
This should be good.
The real lighting will make everything
pop even more.
Is there anything you’re hung up on?
You.
Hey.
There are lots of people here.
Let’s switch to the next set.
Okay.
Let’s go, you two.
Tawan, you can take a break.
Aran, please change your outfits.
Next, we’ll do solo shots of Aran
with the product.
It’s almost time for the meeting
with the Hong Kong team.
We still have half an hour.
Don’t do this.
Go upstairs to prepare for the meeting.
I’ll take it from here.
Trust me.
I’ll leave it to you.
Of course.
Okay. We have 10 minutes.
Ready, Ran?
Ran?
Are you okay?
Give me a second.
My eye hurts.
Do you want me to take a look?
Look up for me.
Hey!
I told you to stay
the hell away from Ran!
Don’t hurt Peach.
Why not?
You're protecting him so much, huh?
You love him so much, huh?
I hate you so damn much for
always acting like this.
What does that mean?
You chose him?
Stop being like this and take a hard look
at yourself, will you?
You can’t take care of anyone
because you keep acting like
a demanding kid.
You’re calling me a kid?
Stop it!
Hey!
The power’s out!
Go check if something’s broken.
Tawan’s gone!
Oh!
Where did he go?
Hey.
You got hurt again, Peachayarat.
Are you sure you don’t want to
go to the hospital?
At least have a doctor check you.
You have a bruise.
It’s nothing.
Dropping a phone on my face
hurts more than this.
Are you sure you’re okay?
Can you put some ointment on it for me?
Me?
Plub! Plub!
Something big happened.
What happened?
Tawan got into a fight with Peach
at the studio.
Where’s Peach now?
At the studio?
Well…
Nuch, where’s Peach?
The CEO took Peach upstairs.
Huh?
Why?
It’s clear now.
What’s clear?
The CEO and Peach…
Wouldn’t it be better
to have a doctor do this for you?
It’s nothing serious.
Let’s not bother an emergency doctor.
But I…
I don’t know how to do this.
Give me your hand.
I’m afraid of accidentally hurting you.
Just be gentle, and it won’t hurt.
Hey.
I can’t see my own bruise.
You have to look.
Is this too hard?
No.
You’re at ARSENI,
but you ended up getting hurt.
I’m really useless.
It was so sudden.
No one could’ve prepared for it.
Don’t blame yourself.
Where’s Tawan, by the way?
You didn’t do anything to him, did you?
I just had people
throw him out of the company.
Is that all?
That’s really all.
If you don’t believe me, check the CCTV.
He even drove off by himself.
You’ve gotten much calmer, you know?
I know.
Because if this were me before,
not even his name
would be left in this world.
How cruel.
Whose boyfriend are you?
I forbid you
from getting hurt
or getting any more wounds,
under any circumstances.
Is that even something you can forbid?
Staff from other floors
aren’t allowed on this floor.
Then I quit.
Ms. Panachakorn.
Peach!
The CEO?
What’s the meaning of this?
(Sorry, it’s not possible
to reach the number…)
to reach the number you’ve dialed…)
(Sorry, it’s not possible…)
Ran.
Ran, hear me out.
I did everything I did because I love you.
So Punching Peach
was your way of loving me?
Peach?
You’re mentioning his name again.
Isn’t this all his fault?
I’ll say this one last time.
Peach is my big brother.
Big brother?
Big brother, huh?
Weren’t you about to suck lips?
The one I love is you, Tawan!
It’s always been you!
But thanks to today,
I can finally stop loving you.
No.
Listen to me, Ran.
Hear me out.
Hey!
Ran, hear me out.
What?
I’m sorry, Ran.
I guess we really won’t work out, Tawan.
Ran, I’m sorry.
Ran. Ran.
Ran.
Can you leave me alone?
There’s only one thing I’m asking you.
I want my life back.
Stop bothering me already.
I can’t even be friends with you!
Ran, can you hear me out?
Ran.
Go wherever you want!
Gosh!
So…you two…
are already boyfriends?
Damn.
Please don’t be rude.
You…
and the CEO?
Are you really dating?
Just call me Mr. Thee.
Or if there’s an opportunity,
you can call me P’Thee.
I’m your brother’s boyfriend.
So I’m basically your other brother,
Panachakorn.
So, Peach,
you don’t have anything to say to me?
Whatever you want to say to me,
just say it.
Mr. Thee,
do you really love Peach?
Whatever you want me to swear to,
just tell me.
But aren’t you a mafia boss?
You’re so scary.
Why isn’t Peach scared of you?
What you see is just a made-up story
that the outsiders believe.
I’m not like that.
But I only have one brother.
I mean,
Peach is the only one I have.
To be honest, I’m possessive of him.
I’m afraid he’ll love you more than me.
Peach has dated many people,
but I’ve never felt my heart
sink this much before.
Do I seem that dangerous in your eyes?
No.
It’s just that Peach
seems to really love you.
You say you two only have
each other, right?
What’s wrong with having
one more big brother?
You know how to be a brother?
Why not?
I have a younger brother myself.
We actually have something in common.
What is that?
We both...
love Peachayarat.
It’s not the same.
I love him more.
Alright.
You love him a little more than I do.
Wouldn’t it be better
if we were on the same team?
The same team?
Our team’s mission is to make Peachayarat
happy for the rest of his life.
Deal?
Tap it.
Mr. Tatsuya wants to see you
in order to take responsibility
for the damage that happened.
They’re happy to send another model
from their agency to replace Tawan.
We won’t work with that company again.
We’ll also cancel all the jobs
they’ve already booked Peach for.
Will Mr. Peach be okay with that?
I’ve already talked to him.
Besides, I couldn’t interfere
with his work before
because we weren’t anything yet.
But now we’re dating.
That means I can cuddle Peach.
I said it’s “meddle”, Boss.
Yeah.
I can do everything.
We also heard from
the Weera-arpakorn, Tawan’s family.
They want to send a lawyer to negotiate
the lawsuit we filed for damages
for their assault on Peach.
I don’t want to see anyone.
When they were causing all that mess,
no one bothered to ask for my permission.
Now they’re in trouble,
and they want to negotiate?
That’s too easy, isn’t it?
I promised Peach no one would get hurt,
but you can handle everything else.
Make them learn their lesson
for daring to hurt my man.
Yes, Boss.
When did you two secretly plan this?
We didn’t sneak around.
We just planned a family meal.
I want to eat salmon.
Do you want the whole salmon?
Let me take care of that.
That’s too much.
Half of it then.
Plub.
Just kidding.
But I’m not kidding.
When we get a chance,
I’ll take you fishing in Iceland,
then watch the Aurora. What do you say?
Sounds good.
Stop it, brother and sister.
Is the power out?
But I already paid the electricity bill.
VILLAGE GROUP CHAT
MANAGEMENT: A CAR HIT A POWER POLE
AND A TRANSFORMER EXPLODED.
WE’RE GETTING TECHNICIANS
TO REPAIR IT. @ALL
A car hit a power pole.
The power will probably be back tomorrow.
That’s too bad.
What should we do?
You say it’s bad,
but you’re smiling from ear to ear.
I’m not smiling.
Are you seeing things?
I might have to trouble you to—
Sure.
Drop me off at Plub’s condo.
Oh?
That’s not what I had in mind.
What did you have in mind, you sneaky?
My house is so much closer
than Plub’s condo.
This is your house?
Let’s get inside.
If it were me,
I wouldn’t even dare call this a house.
It’s yours.
Are you crazy?
Oh, it’s okay. I’ll carry this myself.
Isn’t that Ms. Natlada?
Ms. Nat was still young here.
You know her?
She was so famous when I was a kid.
She’s your mom?
I need private time.
Whoa.
This is your bedroom?
Our bedroom.
Hold on.
So you love watching soap operas
because…?
Yes.
It makes me feel close to my mom.
Are you okay?
Of course.
It can’t hurt me anymore.
Are you lonely?
I used to be,
but I have you now.
Mr. Thee!
Go take a bath.
I’ll get you the kind of pajamas
a normal person would wear.
I really want to know,
between your pajamas and mine,
which one is closer to being normal.
Why did you come in?
I’m going to take a bath.
I want you to brush my teeth again.
Where’s your babysitter gang?
I told everyone I needed privacy.
And?
That means no one can come up
to intrude anymore.
Usually, I have people brush my teeth
and give me a bath.
Mr. Thee.
Now I only have you.
Mr. Thee is upstairs, right?
Yes.
Mr. Mok,
Mr. Thee ordered that
no one go up and disturb him.
(Peachayarat Jane-kit?)
(Is there something I should know
about this name?)
You’re really not going to soak with me?
No.
My instincts tell me it’s dangerous.
Is this really necessary?
Theerakit Kian Lee.
In Hong Kong, my relative died
from using soap with poison.
Since then,
all items must be safety-checked first.
But that was a long time ago.
It was probably even before I was born.
It’s a gunshot wound.
Luckily, it was just a graze.
But it left a mark until now.
I’m fine now.
Don’t worry.
You said you wouldn’t allow me
to be wounded or hurt again.
The same goes for you. Got it?
Can you promise me
that no matter what happens,
we’ll get through it together?
Didn’t you say the world you’re building
will be just the two of us?
Don’t worry, Mr. Thee.
There’s one thing I want to ask of you.
Hmm?
I want you to call my name.
You mean call you...
Mr. Thee?
Kian.
Can I really call you that?
Only my family is allowed
to call me by my middle name.
Now, you’re my lover.
Kian.
P’Kian.
Huh?
I want you to call me P’Kian.
P’Kian.
Peach loves you, P’Kian.
♪ On a dark starless night,
I’ll still be there ♪
♪ Nothing will change my mind, I swear ♪
♪ I will always love you
for all that you are ♪
♪ Every part of you
belongs to my whole heart ♪
♪ Remember I'm with you no matter where ♪
♪ I will always love you for all time ♪
♪ Let me tend to your heart ♪
I thought you said it was dangerous.
Aren’t you scared anymore?
I was just saying that.
Otherwise, I couldn’t be with you,
Mr. Thee.
What did you just call me?
I said it out of habit.
Then you have to practice
until you’re used to it.
Try calling me P’Kian.
P’Kian.
That’s so good.
I love it.
Can you try saying it like...
you miss me so much?
P’Kian.
Oh.
I love it.
Now, can you call me in a lovey-dovey way?
Try it.
P’Kian.
This time, can you say it in a sulky way?
Even when you’re scolding me,
your voice sounds beautiful.
So, I want you to call me P’Kian—
Come on!
P’Kian!
How many more versions of Kian
do you want today?
Just give me one more version.
Whisper next to my ear
and wish me good night before I sleep.
Get a grip, P’Kian!
You’re crazy.
This is crazy.
I’m so shy.
What happened to Tawan,
was it your doing?
Yes.
Did you really have to
threaten me like that?
Good night.
I want to sleep over here.
Next time.
I give you permission to move some
of your necessary stuff here.
Now that you said that,
please get ready
to have your house renovated.
Call me when you get home.
Hello.
(Mr. Mok, Mr. Thee forgot his phone
at my house.)
Mr. Mok?
What’s that sound?